[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question" : "Which of the following is a popular JavaScript library for building user interfaces?",
        "options": [
            "Angular",
            "Vue.js",
            "React",
            "Svelte"
        ],
        "answer": "React"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question" : "Which CSS framework is known for its utility-first approach?",
        "options": [
            "Bootstrap",
            "Tailwind CSS",
            "Foundation",
            "Bulma"
        ],
        "answer": "Tailwind CSS"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question" : "Which tool is commonly used for bundling JavaScript modules?",
        "options": [
            "Webpack",
            "Gulp",
            "Grunt",
            "Parcel"
        ],
        "answer": "Webpack"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question" : "Which of the following is a state management library for React?",
        "options": [
            "Redux",
            "Vuex",
            "MobX",
            "NgRx"
        ],
        "answer": "Redux"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question" : "Which HTML element is used to define a client-side script?",
        "options": [
            "<script>",
            "<style>",
            "<link>",
            "<meta>"
        ],
        "answer": "<script>"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question" : "Which of the following is a CSS preprocessor?",
        "options": [
            "Sass",
            "PostCSS",
            "Less",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question" : "Which of the following is a JavaScript package manager?",
        "options": [
            "npm",
            "Yarn",
            "Bower",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question" : "Which of the following is used to style React components?",
        "options": [
            "CSS Modules",
            "Styled Components",
            "Emotion",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question" : "Which of the following is a tool for testing React components?",
        "options": [
            "Jest",
            "Mocha",
            "Chai",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "Jest"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question" : "Which of the following is a method to fetch data in React?",
        "options": [
            "fetch API",
            "Axios",
            "GraphQL",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    }
]